Guide to the Joseph Strauss Bridge Plans, 1905-1935 M0163
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Bascule Draw Bridge. Arlington Memorial Bridge Commission, 1927 -1928; File 1310:; (82). (Roll 79)
- Bascule Draw Bridge. Arlington Memorial Bridge Commission, 1927; File 1310:; (21). (Roll 80)
- Burnside Bridge, Portland, Oregon, 1923; File 1370: S.T.B.B.; (37). (Roll 81)
- Hamoul Bridge, Egyptian State Railways, 1914; File 831: S.T.B.B.; (33). (Roll 82)
- Causeway from Mare Island to Vallejo, California, 1918; File 833: S.T.B.B.; (15). (Roll 83)
- Jackson Street Bridge, South Branch of the Chicago River, 1913; File 632: S.T.B.B.; (86). (Roll 84)
- Polk Street Bridge, South Branch of the Chicago River, 1908; File ---- S.T.B.B.; (23). (Roll 85)
- Channel Street Waterway at Third Street, San Francisco California, 1931 -1932; File 1038: S.T.B.B.; (40). (Roll 86)
- New Mare Island to Vallejo Causeway, California, 1933; File 1058: S.T.B.B.; (12). (Roll 86)
- Quogue Canal, Westhampton Beach, New York, 1935; File 1167: S.T.B.B.; (20). (Roll 86)
- Beach Thorofare, Atlantic County, New Jersey, 1917; File 991: S.T.B.B.; (7). (Roll 87)
- Broad Thorofare, Atlantic County, New Jersey, 1915; File 934: S.T.B.B.; (7). (Roll 87)
- Boca Ciega Causeway Bridge, 1926; File 1055: S.T.B.B.; (7). (Roll 87)
- North Branch of the Chicago River for the Chicago & Northwestern Railway, 1914; File 560: S.T.B.B.; (29). (Roll 88)
- Keating's Channel, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1915 -1916; File 864: S.T.B.B.; (22). (Roll 89)
- South Fork of the South Branch of the Chicago River, File ---- S.T.B.B.; (7). (Roll 90)
- New Bridge, Port of Calcutta, India, 1911; File 400: S.T.B.B.; (10). (Bundle Bundle A)
- Calumet River, Chicago, Illinois, 1909; File 404: S.T.B.B.; (21). (Bundle Bundle A)
- Kaministiqua River, Canadian Pacific Railway, 1910; File 405: S.T.B.B.; (35). (Bundle Bundle A)
- Welland Canal Feeder, Niagara, St. Catharines & Toronto Railway Co., 1910; File 409: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Bundle Bundle A)
- Buzzards Bay, Massachusetts, 1909; File 413: S.T.B.B.; (21). (Bundle Bundle A)
- Ny Knippels Bro, Copenhagen, Denmark, 1906; File 5: S.T.B.B.; (l0). (Bundle Bundle B)
- Three Ribbed Concrete Steel Bridge. Kishwaukee River, near Belvedere, Illinois, 1906; File 8:; (17). (Bundle Bundle B)
- Swan Creek, Toledo, Ohio, 1908; File 38: S.T.B.B.; (14). (Bundle Bundle B)
- Cuyahoga & Wabash Railroad at Cleveland, Ohio, 1904; File 121: S.T.B.B.; (24). (Bundle Bundle B)
- Illinois River, La Salle County, Illinois, 1909; File 221: S.T.B.B.; (4). (Bundle Bundle B)
- Elizabeth River, Elizabeth, New Jersey, 1907; File 251: S.T.B.B.; (7). (Bundle Bundle B)
- Palace Bridge, St. Petersburg, Russia, 1911 -1912; File 365: S.T.B.B.; (74). (Bundle Bundle C)
- Illinois River Bridge, Peoria, Illinois, 1909; File 366: S.T.B.B.; (17). (Bundle Bundle C)
- Fox River, Green Bay, Wisconsin, 1907 -1908; File 260: S.T.B.B.; (18). (Bundle Bundle D)
- Cuyahoga River, Cleveland, Ohio, 1910-1911; File 309: S.T.B.B.; (21). (Bundle Bundle D)
- Red River, for the National Transcontinental Railway, 1909; File 333: S.T.B.B.; (7). (Bundle Bundle D)
- New River and Pablo Creek Bridges, Fort Lauderdale, Florida, 1909; File 1QX: S.T.B.B.; (7). (Bundle Bundle E)
- Assiniboine River, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1909 -1910; File 367: S.T.B.B.; (11). (Bundle Bundle E)
- Elizabeth River, Elizabeth, New Jersey, 1915; File 371: S.T.B.B.; (11). (Bundle Bundle E)
- Hackensack River, Erie Railroad, 1910 -1911; File 395: S.T.B.B.; (21). (Bundle Bundle E)
- Overpack Creek, Little Ferry, New Jersey, 1909-1910; File 396: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Bundle Bundle E)
- New United States Ship Canal, Sault Ste. Marie, Michigan, 1910 -1912; File 399: S.T.B.B.; (35). (Bundle Bundle E)
- Miami & Erie Canal, Lockland, Ohio, 1905; File 1: S.T.B.B.; (15). (Bundle Bundle F)
- Rahway River, Rahway, New Jersey, 1906; File 3: S.T.B.B.; (26). (Bundle Bundle F)
- Coopers Creek, Camden, New Jersey, 1906; File 4: S.T.B.B.; (35). (Bundle Bundle F)